jennifersbody.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

**_Privacy Policy_**

**  Effective June 23, 2011:**

Summary of the Foxconnect.com (the "Website") Privacy Policy:

1.              **INTRODUCTION –** The Introduction identifies the basic Website Services covered by this Privacy Policy and provides a brief overview of what this Privacy Policy covers. 

2.              **SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION -** This section addresses the types of information that the Website collects directly from users and the collection of non-personally identifiable information via cookies and related technologies by, and on behalf of, the Website and third parties.

3.              **NOTICE AND CHOICE -** This section provides information on users' options to control how their information is collected and used, how the Website notifies users about future Policy changes, where the Website stores data, and third-party web sites that may link to the Website Services.

4.              **USE AND DISCLOSURE -** This section describes how the Website uses your information to provide and manage the Website Services, including when the Website may disclose your information to third parties that assist the Website in providing those services.  

5.              **SECURITY -** This section describes the Website's security measures. 

6.              **USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELATION -** This section informs users how to access and change their personal information stored by the Website, and how to cancel their accounts.

7.              **CONTACT US -** This section instructs users how to contact the Website.

**1.          INTRODUCTION**

Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment LLC ("Company" or "we") operates Foxconnect.com, and the services Company provides on the Website include services related to promoting, advertising and/or purchasing certain Company products, including when the Website is accessed via the Internet, mobile or other device (collectively, the "Website Services").  The Website is part of the United States based operations of News Corporation.

As set forth in our Terms of Use http://www.foxconnect.com/terms_of_use, the Website is a general audience site, is not targeted to children, and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all "users," including both those who use some of the Website Services without being registered and those who have registered with the Website.  This Privacy Policy describes the Website's collection and use of users' personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address).  It also describes generally the Website's practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account.

**2.          SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON WEBSITE SERVICES**

_User Submitted Information.   _

**Registration Information** is the information that users must provide to Company in order to register for a Website Service, for example, your full name, email address, mailing address, credit card information or telephone number.. When we collect Registration Information from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats, bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. __

**Public Information and Posts** consists of comments or content that you post to the Website Services and the information about you that accompanies those posts, such as a username or user picture.  Your Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and will be displayed in search results both on the Website Services and on external search engines.

_Website Collected Information._

**Website Site Activity Information.** When users access the Website Services, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits.  For example, in order to permit your connection to the Website Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information.  If you access the Website Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it.  We also may use cookies and other tracking technologies (including browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier.  Web sites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site.  We may use these technologies to collect and store information about usage of the Website Services, such as pages our visitors have viewed, search queries that have run been run, and advertisements our visitors have seen. If Company wishes to combine your personal information with information we obtain through these technologies in order to determine what messages the Website provides to you, we will obtain your express affirmative consent. 

Third parties that support the Website Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as website hosting, customer service, product purchase services (including order, fulfillment and payment authorization and processing services), fraud prevention and investigation, data analysis and promotional assistance (including sending communications and creating, administering and operating contests, sweepstakes or other games), allowing users to share content or tracking aggregate site usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information.  The Website does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies.  For more information about third-party ad networks that use these technologies, see [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether.  Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies).  Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe's website, see [http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/). Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through the Website Services.

**Third Parties.   **To improve the quality of the Website Services, we may supplement the information we collect with information from third parties.  If you access the Website Services through a third-party connection or log-in, we may also collect your user ID and/or user name associated with that third-party service, and any information you have made public in connection with that service or which the third party shares with partner services. 

  **3.         NOTICE & CHOICE**

**Means of Notice and Choice.   **This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which the Website provides you with notice about its collection and use of your personal information.   The Website will not use your personal information in a manner different from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your permission. 

**Privacy Policy Changes.   **The **** Website may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary.  If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent through email or a prominent posting on the Website.

**Location of Data.   **The Website Services are hosted in the United States.  If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States.  U.S. data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction.  As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Websites.   **The Website Services may also be linked to sites operated by website affiliates (i.e., that are part of the News America Group: "[Affiliated Companies](http://www.newscorp.com/)") or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, games or applications developed and maintained by third parties. The Website is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Website Services via a link, enable a third-party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third-party site.  Additionally, although all Affiliated Companies adhere to the News Corporation corporate [Privacy Principles](http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html), users who visit an Affiliated Company site should still refer to its separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. 

**4.          USE AND DISCLOSURE**

_Information Made Public Through Use of the Website Services_

Some applications on the Website may permit you to post information publically available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers and anyone else with access to the Website Services.  Other applications on the Website may permit you to share information only with those individual email addresses provided by you or with other users of third party social networks to which you belong, consistent with the privacy settings of you and other users of such third party social network sites. 

_Website's Use and Disclosure of Information_

We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy.  In addition, the Website may share your personal information with Affiliated Companies. 

We use the information we collect from and about users for the following purposes:

**To provide and manage the Website Services**.  We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the Website Services and features to you including to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to provide you with customer support, and to respond to inquiries.  We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the Website Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.    

**To allow third-party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Website Services.**   The Website may make your personal information available to certain third-party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Website Services.  These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to the Website. 

**To deliver relevant advertising.**  We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the Website Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit the Website Services.  We may work with third-party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you.  We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the Website Services. As noted above, these third-party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.  To find out more about third-party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative website http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.   

**To contact you.** The Website may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications related to the Website Services to the email address you provided to us at registration or to your account.  If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from the Website, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are a member, such as notifications of changes to the Website Services or policies. 

**To protect the rights of the Website and our users.   **There may be instances when the Website may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where the Website has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of the Website, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Website Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. 

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.   **If the Website sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, the Website may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**5.          SECURITY**

The Website uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information and credit card information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

**6.          ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE**

Visitors to the Website may review the Registration Information we maintain about them in our records whenever possible. If you would like to review, correct, or delete this information, please contact the Website at:

Fox Connect C/O Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment Online  
2816 Columbia Street  
Torrance, CA 90503  
Telephone:(888) 223-4369  
International Callers: (310) 217-4764  
Fax: (888) 443-4369  
Email: privacypolicy@foxhome.com

Unless otherwise indicated by Company, your usual operator rates apply to all telephone, email, SMS or other communications. 

Remember that even after you request deletion, copies of some information may remain viewable in some circumstances – where, for example, you have shared information with a third-party application or website.  We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies.  Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet and from search engines. 

**7.**          **CONTACT US**

 If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact the Website at:

Email: privacypolicy@foxhome.com

Mail: Fox Connect  
C/O Twentieth Century Fox Home Entertainment Online  
2816 Columbia Street  
Torrance, CA 90503  
Telephone: (888) 223-4369  
International Callers: (310) 217-4764  
Fax: (888) 443-4369 

Unless otherwise indicated by the Website, your usual operator rates apply to all telephone, email, SMS or other communications.
